Guide to the Saybrook College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1964-2010 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Saybrook College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1964-2010 maintained by the dean
1961-2010
RU 172
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
100.58
(148 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Saybrook College, Yale University.
Saybrook College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-K-1 (YRG 13-K-1), Records of the dean of Saybrook College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Saybrook College, Yale University.
College students; Saybrook College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Classes of 1964-1965, 1959-1965; Accession 1971-A-008
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - Class of 1964
    - Non-graduates
  - Class of 1965
    - Non-graduates
      - Resignations, drop-outs, leaves of absence, 1960-1965 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Student records for the Class of 1966, 1962-1966; Accession 19ND-A-310
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2045 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
- Student records for the Class of 1967, Accession 19ND-A-311
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2046 as established by Yale Corporation regulations. January 1, 2046
- Student records for the Class of 1968, Accession 19ND-A-312
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2046 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
- Student records for the Class of 1969, Accession 19ND-A-313
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2049 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
- Student records for the Class of 1970, Accession 19ND-A-314
- Student records for the Class of 1971, Accession 19ND-A-315
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2051 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
- Student records for the Class of 1972, 1968-1972; Accession 19ND-A-316
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2048
  - Non-graduates
- Student records for the Class of 1973, 1969-1973; Accession 1977-A-018
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2049
- Student records for the Class of 1974, 1970-1974; Accession 19ND-A-317
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
  - Non-graduates
- Student records for the Classes of 1975-1976, 1971-1976; Accession 1980-A-022
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
- Student records for the Class of 1975-1978 (impounded), 1971-1978; Accession 1975-A-016; 3.75; (5 boxes)
  Restricted until 2054.
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
  - Class of 1977
  - Class of 1978
- Student records for the Class of 1977, 1973-1977; Accession 1982-A-036
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
- Student records for the Class of 1978, 1974-1978; Accession 1983-A-063
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1974-1978 (Box 4)
- Student records for the Class of 1979, 1975-1979; Accession 1984-A-040
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  - Ex-students, incomplete records
- Student records for the Class of 1980, 1976-1980; Accession 1985-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  - Incomplete records (did not graduate)
- Student records for the Class of 1981, 1977-1981; Accession 1987-A-011
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Incomplete Records:
- Student records for the Class of 1982, 1978-1982; Accession 1988-A-002
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Incomplete Records
- Student records for the Class of 1983, 1979-1983; Accession 1988-A-103
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
- Student records for the Class of 1984, 1980-1984; Accession 1989-A-112
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Incomplete Records: (non-grads)
- Student records for the Class of 1985, 1981-1985; Accession 1990-A-129
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
- Student records for the Class of 1986, 1982-1986; Accession 1991-A-106
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
- Student records for the Class of 1987, 1983-1987; Accession 1992-A-068
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
- Student records for the Class of 1988, 1984-1988; Accession 1994-A-010
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1989, 1985-1989; Accession 1994-A-145
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1990, 1986-1990; Accession 1995-A-072
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1991, 1987-1991; Accession 1996-A-073
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1992, 1988-1992; Accession 1997-A-095
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1993, 1989-1993; Accession 1999-A-001
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1994, 1990-1994; Accession 1999-A-095
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1995, 1991-1995; Accession 2000-A-053
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  - Tentative
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1996, 1992-1996; Accession 2001-A-163
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1997, 1993-1997; Accession 2003-A-014
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
  - Tentative
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1998, 1994-1998; Accession 2004-A-021
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - Class list (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1999, 1995-1999; Accession 2005-A-059
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
  - Class list, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Non-graduate
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 2000, 1996-2000; Accession 2006-A-099
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - Deceased
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 2001, 1997-2001; Accession 2008-A-022
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 2002, 1998-2002; Accession 2009-A-034
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
  - Withdrawn Students
- Student records for the Classes of 2003-2005, 1998-2005; Accession 2014-A-021
  Restricted until January 1, 2080
  - Class of 2003
    - Withdrawn
  - Class of 2004
  - Class of 2005
- Student records for the Classes of 2006 through 2008, 2002-2008; Accession 2018-A-019
  Restricted until January 1, 2084
  - Class of 2006
  - Class of 2007
  - Class of 2008
    - Class of 2008 information, 2004-2008 (Box 4, Folder 26A)
- Student records for the Classes of 2009-2010, 2004-2010; Accession 2019-A-0013
  Restricted until January 1, 2087
  - Class of 2009
    - Anderson, Todd, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Au, Tony, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Babarsky, Joseph Edward, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bell, Jared David, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Belo-Osagie, Jamilla-withdrawn, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Berwick, Elissa Matz, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bilow, Michael Aaron, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bitran, Eva Lucia, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Blas, Lauren Margout, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Boone, Christine Elizabeth, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Brien, Willaim Warren, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Caldwell, Michael David, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Castillo, Rodolfo, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Cheung, Tina, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Chiles, Clay Benton, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Chu, Esther Ning, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Clarke, Edward Bullard, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Coe, Jacqueline Christine, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Cordero, Melina Sara, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Cronson, Elizabeth M, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Currey, Kevin Thomas, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Czyrnik, Rebecca Ann, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Dale, Darius A., 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Dewechter, Patrick Francis, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Dominitz, Alexander Duncanson, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Eigen, Jacob, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Eisenson, Matthew Benjamin, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Everhart, Edwin Keely, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Fodor, Ryan James, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Fragapane, Taylor Kathryn, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Gangji, Alizeh N., 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Gasner, Katherine Weil, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Geels, Jeffrey Michael, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Geist, Bryan G., 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Gilliland, Thomas Candler, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Glandorf, Lee Juliana, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Gombeski, Christopher Douglas, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Gong, Kyle Forrest, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Gordon, Valerie Ann, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Granor, Nathaniel, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Grant, Martha Elizabeth, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Green, Kevin McClure, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Griffin, Craig William-withdrawn, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Guo, Nan, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Hays, Foster Ahn, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Hinkle, John William, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Huang, Jing, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Hughes, Sarah Kathleen, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Jacks, Jordan Randall, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Jacobs, Benjamin Daniel, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Jannise, Justin Ray, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - John-Lewis, Tracey Renee, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Johnston, Peter Nathaniel, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Jones, Amy Elizabeth, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Jones, Shane, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Josselyn, Brandon Craig, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Kafura, Craig James, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Kazimer, Katherine Elizabeth, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Kendrick, Katharine Anne, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Kim, Chang Young, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Klein, Andrew Philip, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Klein, Eric Joseph, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Klein, Matthew Richard, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Kozlowski, Piotr Jakub, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Krenchel, Mikkel Kruger, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Lall, Natasha Tilak, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Lawrence, Noah Joshua, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Lawson, April Angeline, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Lechner, Emily Clancy, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Lee, Sun Jin, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Lewis, Daniel Dise-withdrawn, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Li, Han, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Lopez, Carolos Alberto, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Luehring-Jones, Peter Theodore, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - MacQueen, Grant Robert, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Markovitz, Adam Alexander, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Marshman, Victoria, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - McAuliffe, Caitlin Ligia, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - McClement, Joelson Marc-Anthony, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Medina, Luis, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Miller, Erin Lynn, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery, Stacia Janise, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Murphy, Eamon P., 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Narotsky, David L., 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Nevin, Camila Maria, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Noh, Janet Youngeun, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - O'Neill, Kevin Benjamin-withdrawn, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Park, Christine, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Park, Jane, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Person, Christine Elaine, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Plattus, Rachel Berliner, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Potteiger, Jaymie Leigh, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Quigley, Robert Jacob, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Rae-Grant, robert Tucker, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Resor, Helen L., 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Roberts, Anika Renee, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Robinson, John Jerry, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Rodrigues, Ryan John-Paul, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Roosth, David Lawrence, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Sauer, Jordan Frederick, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Schussler, Victoria Ilanna, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Schwartz, Alexandra Lily, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Shah, Aniket Akshay, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Simmons, Jarren Christian, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Smith, Caroline Anne, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Stackhouse, Spencer Davis, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Stilwell, Justin, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Stoller, Heather Michele, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Swett, Brooks Tucker, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Tai, Che Yu Jeffrey, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Tannen, Benjamin Eric, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Tetreault, Daniel Thomas, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Torres, Danielle Rose, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Vainshtein, Mitchell Steven, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Wagner, Andrew David, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Warden, Jennifer Chase, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Warrick-Alexander, James, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Wayman, Abraham Mark, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Weissberg, Elizabeth Wright, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Wheatley, Brandon Alexander, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - White, Edward Andrew, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Xu, Hao, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Yin, Ti, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Zink, Michael Robert, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Class of 2010
    - Allen, Emma, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Ammirati, Julianne, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Anantua, Richard, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Anderson, Austin, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Andersson, Hans, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Angelopoulos, Nikolaos (Nick), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Anklesaria, Farhad, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Arntson, Emily (Emily), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Atir, Stav, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Baneman, Daniel (Dan), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Barry-Heffernan, Caitlin (Caity), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Bhaloo, Imran (Imu), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Blum, Julia, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Brotherton, Carolyn, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Bryan, Chacey (Chace), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Carballo, Jessica, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Carter, Jordan (Jordan), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Chang, Edward, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Chen, Isabel (Izzy), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Chiu, Kevin, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Chukumba, Justin (Jay), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Colantonio, Stephanie, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Conroy, Michelle, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Corrigan-Gibbs, Henry, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - del Valle, Vanessa, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Diamond, Marie, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Donohue, Lauren, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Dunn, Michael, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Ellison, Tim Charles, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Ettinger, Katharine, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Feinstein, Ross, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Flores, Benjamin (Ben), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Friedman, Gabriel (Gabe), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Galambos, Kathryn, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Galvez, Jessica, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Galvin, Audrianna (Audi), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Gause, Trenton (Trent), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Gayer, Carlin (Carlin), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Gilliland, Jason (Jason), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Goffman, Gabriel (Gabe), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Gogel, Evan, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Golden, Michael (Leslie), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Goldman, Max, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Gordon, Claire, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Grunes, Marissa, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Grunyk, John, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Haliburton, Adam, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Halpern, Ian, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Hamilton, Malcolm, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Holley, William (Will), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Hopkins, Jeremy, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Istel, Cordelia, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Jacobsen, Nora, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Jenda, Emily, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Johns, Susan, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Johnson, Carl, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Kimovec, Farrah, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - King, Matthew, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - LaBoone, Holly, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Lang, Margo, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Lee, Amy, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Lee, Mihan, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Lee, Taylor, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Leon, Melissa, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Levander, Samuel (Sam), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Li, Jian, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Lieberman, Allyson, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Lu, Mindy, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Luo, Lisa, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Maltby, Katherine (Kate), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Margines, Jack (Ben), 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Marks, Zachary (Zach), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - May, Grant, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - McComish, Julie, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - McGhee, Davida, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - McLaughlin, Allison, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Meyer, Jacob (Jake), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Kelley, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Noel, Leon-withdrawn, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Olson, Elizabeth (Liz), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Omiyi, Angela (Angie), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Otus, Hanim (Basak), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Palmer, Cory, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Porter, David, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Poverman, Marisa, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Pulido, Vina, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Rafferty, Madeleine, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Ramos, Jennifer, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Regan, Eileen, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Resor, George, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Rhee, Jessica (Jessie), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Richards, Stephanie, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Riederer, Christopher (Chris), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Robery, Nicholas-withdrawn, 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Sanchez, Nicholas (Nick), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Sarwar, Shejuti, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Sexton, Katherine (Katie), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Sheard, Yumiko, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Short, Elaine, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Siegel, Sarah, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Silverman, Samuel, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Singer, George, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Smith, Hannah, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Smith, Matthew, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Snell, Jake, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Srivastava, Amar, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Tan, Joshua (Josh), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Torbati, Yeganeh (June), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Tormey, James (Jim), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Trigo, Natalie (Natalie), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Twarek, Bryan, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Udelsman, Andrew, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Ueyama, Shawna, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Urgilez, Jennifer, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Venning, Crystal, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Vrolyk, John, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - West, Lee, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Wibecan, Leah, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Woo, Justin, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Wright, Shaina, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Yang, Ge, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Yang, Phillip, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Zielenbach, Molly, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 52)